http://www.vibratronics.com/default.php?id=policy

Privacy Policy
At Vibratronics, we understand and respect your concern about the privacy of any information you supply while visiting our web site. We believe that knowledge is the key to monitoring and protecting how your information is used on the Internet. This statement sets forth Vibratronics Privacy Policy and describes the practice Vibratronics follows with respect to all visitors to all our sites worldwide.
Personal information
Vibratronics collects certain personal information from users of this site. Guests are required to provide certain personal information in order to receive requested material, requested phone call, or access certain parts of our sites, and authorized users must provide certain contact and account information in order to access and download images. We use this information for internal purposes to process your order, answer your questions and send you requested information, and to maintain or update your contact information. For Vibratronics Partners we gather your information to send you updates about special offers, new products, special promotions, and noteworthy news and events. Vibratronics does not sell or rent information about its customers to third parties. Vibratronics may only share contact information with its partners or affiliates to enable them to provide you with special benefits, promotions, or offers from either Vibratronics or its affiliates and its partners.
Vibratronics may also compile data in aggregate form so that we may better understand and serve the users that are visiting our site. For example, we may produce reports on the most popular search terms by collecting general search term data based on individual searches. Aggregate data is anonymous and does not contain any personal information that identifies a user.
Change of Address or Contact Information
Vibratronics offers the choice to not receive e-mails or updates about special benefits, promotions, or offers from Vibratronics, its affiliates, or its partners. If you no longer wish to receive these updates, or you wish to unsubscribe, please complete our Contact Us form and let us know in the comments section that you would like to be removed from the mailing list.
Security
Vibratronics invests in providing the most secure information exchange on the Internet and has a number of operational functions in place to protect the confidentiality of personal information. However, perfect security on the Internet does not exist, and Vibratronics does not warrant that its site is impenetrable or invulnerable to hackers.
Cookies
When you visit the Vibratronics Web site, Vibratronics sends your computer a cookie, which is a small file that resides on your computer's hard drive and contains non-personally identifiable information about the user. Cookies only identify the user's computer. Cookies allow Vibratronics to make its Web site more useful by storing information about your preferences. You can set your browser's options not to accept cookies, but this may prevent you from accessing all of the features of the Vibratronics Web site.
E-mail
Vibratronics does not rent or sell e-mail lists. Vibratronics may send you e-mail to notify you about your recent order or to answer specific question you might have; this will be sent to the e-mail address you provide to Vibratronics.
Surveys and Contests
Participation in surveys or contests on the Vibratronics Web site is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose personal information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as the industry you are working in, your function, or the size of your plant or shop). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for the purposes of monitoring or improving the use of the Vibratronics Web site.
Links
Please be aware that the Vibratronics Web site may contain links to other sites that are covered by their own privacy policies. Vibratronics is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites and we encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site. We recommend that our users read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.
Changes of Vibratronics Online Privacy Policy
Vibratronics reserves the right to change our online privacy policy. However, we shall not do so without posting those changes on the Vibratronics Web site.If you have any questions about Vibratronics privacy policy or concerns about personal information you have supplied to Vibratronics please contact us by emailing ozdemir@turkmericane.com or calling 1-800-218-3015.
Resources
